(Sheldon:)Well, I think you mean
my friends.
(Sheldon:)And why wasn't
I invited to this?
(Amy:)Maybe because the two of us
being there
(Amy:)would make them feel awkward.
(Sheldon:)We make everyone
feel awkward.
That's our thing!
(Leonard:)They're running
a little behind.
(Leonard:)Should be pretty soon.
Okay.
(Leonard:)Hey, if you're hungry,
there's a breakfast buffet
(Leonard:)at the strip club next door.
(Penny:)Thanks, but I don't like glitter
on my scrambled eggs.
(Leonard:)I don't think the strippers
prepare the meal, but okay.
Look, it-it's not
how I pictured it either,
(Leonard:)but I'm still glad
we're doing it.
(Penny:)Me, too.
You sure?
(Sheldon:)Yes.
And you promise
(Leonard:)you're okay with
everything from the car?
(Penny:)Oh, my God, would you stop
bringing it up?
(Leonard:)You're right.
I'm sorry.
(Leonard:)We have the rest of our lives
(Leonard:)to dredge stuff up from the past
and fight about it.
(Leonard:)So what do you think?
(Leonard:)Should we run next door
and grab a bite?
(Penny:)What if they call our names?
(Leonard:)Oh, don't worry. They gave me
this vibrating coaster.
(Penny:)Oh, and the fairy tale
continues.